<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
  <channel>
    <title>Daily words</title>
    <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top</link>
    <description>每日5分钟，轻松掌握5个英语单词！我们不仅提供词义解释和例句，还将这些单词编织成引人入胜的短篇故事，并配以专属插图。这种视听结合的多感官体验让英语学习既高效又有趣。无论你是初学者还是想扩大词汇量的语言爱好者，都能在这里找到乐趣。订阅我们，让每天的碎片时间绽放语言魅力！</description>
    <language>zh-CN</language>
    <copyright>2024 @daily words</copyright>
    <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
    <itunes:subtitle>Daily words</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>Daily words to improve your English</itunes:summary>
    <itunes:image href="https://files.dwong.top/images/daily-words.png"/>
    <itunes:category text="Education">
      <itunes:category text="English"/>
    </itunes:category>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>dwong</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>admin@daily-words.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:type>episodic</itunes:type>
    <item>
      <title>2024-11-18</title>
      <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top/2024-11-18.html</link>
      <description>eradicate longevity pathetic introvert astronomy&amp;#10;&amp;#10;In a small town, there lived a pathetic introvert named Tom. He often spent his nights gazing at the stars, fascinated by astronomy. One night, while looking through his telescope, he discovered a new star. He decided to name it "Longevity," hoping it would inspire others to eradicate their fears and insecurities. Tom's discovery changed his life. He started to share his passion for astronomy with others, slowly making friends. People who once thought of him as just a pathetic introvert now admired him for his courage and knowledge. Tom realized that even introverts could shine brightly in the world, just like his star, Longevity.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;在一个小镇上，住着一个可怜的内向者汤姆。他常常在夜晚凝视星空，迷恋天文学。一天晚上，当他透过望远镜观察时，他发现了一颗新星。他决定给它命名为“长寿”，希望能激励他人消除恐惧和不安。汤姆的发现改变了他的生活。他开始与他人分享自己对天文学的热情，慢慢交到了朋友。曾经认为他只是一个可怜的内向者的人们，现在因他的勇气和知识而钦佩他。汤姆意识到，即使是内向的人，也能像他的星星“长寿”一样在世界上闪耀。</description>
      <enclosure url="https://files.dwong.top/story/4b661cccf3f7bffc2ff58372314a40f5.mp3" length="786240" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://files.dwong.top/story/4b661cccf3f7bffc2ff58372314a40f5.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 16:02:04 +0800</pubDate>
      <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>2024-11-18</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>eradicate longevity pathetic introvert astronomy</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:image href="https://files.dwong.top/image/4b661cccf3f7bffc2ff58372314a40f5.png"/>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
      <itunes:episode>94</itunes:episode>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024-11-17</title>
      <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top/2024-11-17.html</link>
      <description>twisted blow observant morale blunt&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Once in a small town, there was a twisted tree that stood tall in the park. Many people visited it, and one observant girl named Lily often came to play nearby. She loved to tell stories about the tree and how it had survived many storms. One day, she noticed that the tree seemed sad. Its leaves had started to fall, and the once vibrant branches looked blunt and lifeless. Lily's friend, Tom, saw her worry and suggested they cheer up the tree. They decided to have a small gathering, inviting all the townsfolk to share stories and lift the tree's spirits. The community came together, and soon, the tree was surrounded by laughter and joy. The morale of the town improved, and miraculously, the tree began to bloom again, proving that love and kindness can bring life back to the most twisted of places.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;在一个小镇上，有一棵扭曲的树高高耸立在公园里。很多人来这里，观察的女孩莉莉经常在附近玩耍。她喜欢讲述这棵树的故事，以及它如何在暴风雨中幸存。一天，她注意到树似乎很伤心，树叶开始掉落，曾经充满生机的树枝看上去又钝又死气沉沉。莉莉的朋友汤姆看到她的忧虑，建议他们让树高兴起来。他们决定举行一个小聚会，邀请镇上的所有人分享故事，振奋树的精神。社区聚在一起，很快，树周围充满了笑声和快乐。镇上的士气提高，奇迹般地，树开始再次开花，证明了爱与善良能够让最扭曲的地方重获生机。</description>
      <enclosure url="https://files.dwong.top/story/3f1b5b41bef0d21d7a56d585228a2b16.mp3" length="998400" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://files.dwong.top/story/3f1b5b41bef0d21d7a56d585228a2b16.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 16:02:23 +0800</pubDate>
      <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>2024-11-17</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>twisted blow observant morale blunt</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:image href="https://files.dwong.top/image/3f1b5b41bef0d21d7a56d585228a2b16.png"/>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
      <itunes:episode>93</itunes:episode>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024-11-16</title>
      <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top/2024-11-16.html</link>
      <description>vocation finite mediocre scar arbitrary&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Once upon a time in a small town, there lived a young artist named Clara. She felt her vocation was to create beautiful paintings. However, she often struggled with mediocrity, feeling that her work was merely average. One day, while exploring an old gallery, she found a painting that seemed truly infinite in its beauty. It inspired her to push her limits and break free from the arbitrary rules she had set for herself. Clara decided to paint her feelings without fear of judgment. In the end, her new work was extraordinary, and the town recognized her talent. Clara learned that true art comes from the heart, not from a finite set of expectations.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;从前，在一个小镇上，住着一位年轻的艺术家克拉拉。她觉得自己的天职是创作美丽的画作。然而，她常常感到自己的作品平庸，似乎只是普通而已。一天，她在探索一个古老的画廊时，发现了一幅画，那幅画的美丽似乎是无穷无尽的。它激励她突破自我设定的任意规则，超越自己的极限。克拉拉决定无所畏惧地表达自己的感受，不再担心他人的评判。最终，她的新作品是非比寻常的，镇上的人们都认可了她的才华。克拉拉明白，真正的艺术来自于心灵，而不是有限的期望。</description>
      <enclosure url="https://files.dwong.top/story/e7fc9202b7b766cfdcbdfc27df6f5e12.mp3" length="809760" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://files.dwong.top/story/e7fc9202b7b766cfdcbdfc27df6f5e12.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 16:02:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>2024-11-16</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>vocation finite mediocre scar arbitrary</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:image href="https://files.dwong.top/image/e7fc9202b7b766cfdcbdfc27df6f5e12.png"/>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
      <itunes:episode>92</itunes:episode>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024-11-15</title>
      <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top/2024-11-15.html</link>
      <description>burial disturbed elimination tiresome restructure&amp;#10;&amp;#10;In a small village, a group of workers was sent to restructure an old cemetery. They had to eliminate a few old graves to make space for new ones. However, as they began their work, they discovered that one burial had been disturbed. The old grave was empty, and this caused a tiresome investigation. The villagers were worried about what had happened. They speculated on various reasons for the disturbed burial, from grave robbers to supernatural forces. After several days of searching, they finally found the truth. A curious animal had dug up the grave, searching for food. The villagers were relieved and resumed their work, ensuring the cemetery was treated with respect.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;在一个小村庄里，一群工人被派去重构一个古老的墓地。他们需要消除一些旧墓以为新的墓地腾出空间。然而，当他们开始工作时，发现一个埋葬地点被扰动了。这个古老的墓地是空的，这引发了一场疲惫的调查。村民们对发生了什么感到担忧。他们猜测扰动的埋葬可能是由于盗墓者或超自然力量。经过几天的搜索，他们终于找到了真相。原来是一只好奇的动物挖掘了这个墓地，寻找食物。村民们松了口气，继续他们的工作，确保对这个墓地给予尊重。</description>
      <enclosure url="https://files.dwong.top/story/3bad93933c7e5d8e26aa54a4aea2e7d8.mp3" length="832320" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://files.dwong.top/story/3bad93933c7e5d8e26aa54a4aea2e7d8.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 16:02:16 +0800</pubDate>
      <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>2024-11-15</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>burial disturbed elimination tiresome restructure</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:image href="https://files.dwong.top/image/3bad93933c7e5d8e26aa54a4aea2e7d8.png"/>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
      <itunes:episode>91</itunes:episode>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024-11-14</title>
      <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top/2024-11-14.html</link>
      <description>incur concentration anchor resemblance aspiration&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Once upon a time, in a small village, there was a young girl named Lily. Her greatest aspiration was to become a skilled sailor. Every day, she would watch the ships sailing in the distance, their anchors holding them steady against the waves. One day, she decided to build her own small boat. As she worked on it, she found that she needed to incur the costs of materials, but her concentration on the task was unwavering. When the boat was finished, she noticed how much it resembled the grand ships she admired. With excitement, she set sail for the first time, her dream finally coming true!&amp;#10;&amp;#10;从前，在一个小村庄里，有一个名叫莉莉的小女孩。她最大的梦想是成为一名熟练的水手。每天，她都会观看远处的船只，它们的锚在波浪中稳稳地固定着。有一天，她决定自己建造一只小船。当她在制作时，发现需要承担材料的费用，但她对这项工作的专注毫不动摇。当小船完成时，她注意到它多么像她所欣赏的那些大船。她兴奋地第一次起航，她的梦想终于实现了！</description>
      <enclosure url="https://files.dwong.top/story/accc647418b4ba3a37bbf238e24b2649.mp3" length="735360" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://files.dwong.top/story/accc647418b4ba3a37bbf238e24b2649.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 16:02:18 +0800</pubDate>
      <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>2024-11-14</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>incur concentration anchor resemblance aspiration</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:image href="https://files.dwong.top/image/accc647418b4ba3a37bbf238e24b2649.png"/>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
      <itunes:episode>90</itunes:episode>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024-11-13</title>
      <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top/2024-11-13.html</link>
      <description>unanimously obligatory wing diplomacy instinct&amp;#10;&amp;#10;In a small town, the mayor called for a meeting to discuss an important decision. The townspeople gathered in the community hall. It was unanimously agreed that they needed to improve their town park. Everyone felt it was obligatory to make their town a better place. The mayor, with his charming diplomacy, suggested that they form a committee to oversee the project. A young girl named Lily, with a keen instinct for design, offered to help. As the committee worked together, they created plans for a playground, picnic area, and beautiful flower beds. Their teamwork transformed the park into a vibrant space where everyone could enjoy. It was a wonderful example of how a community can come together to create something special.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;在一个小镇上，市长召开会议，讨论一个重要的决定。镇民们聚集在社区大厅。大家一致认为，他们需要改善镇上的公园。每个人都感到有义务让自己的镇变得更好。市长以其迷人的外交手腕建议成立一个委员会来监督这个项目。一个名叫莉莉的小女孩，对设计有着敏锐的直觉，愿意提供帮助。随着委员会的共同努力，他们为游乐场、野餐区和美丽的花坛制定了计划。他们的团队合作使公园变成了一个充满活力的空间，大家都可以在这里享受。这是一个社区团结一致创造美好事物的绝佳例子。</description>
      <enclosure url="https://files.dwong.top/story/7b4001cc13217570b98d5ddcff4fbba1.mp3" length="899520" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://files.dwong.top/story/7b4001cc13217570b98d5ddcff4fbba1.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 16:02:09 +0800</pubDate>
      <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>2024-11-13</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>unanimously obligatory wing diplomacy instinct</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:image href="https://files.dwong.top/image/7b4001cc13217570b98d5ddcff4fbba1.png"/>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
      <itunes:episode>89</itunes:episode>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024-11-12</title>
      <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top/2024-11-12.html</link>
      <description>inquiry empirical symbolic embody dominant&amp;#10;&amp;#10;In a small town, there was a young girl named Mia who had an inquiry about the stars. She often gazed at the night sky, wondering about the empirical truths of the universe. One evening, her teacher told her that the stars are symbolic of dreams and aspirations. Inspired, Mia wanted to embody these ideals. She decided to build a telescope to observe the stars more closely, believing that knowledge is dominant over ignorance. With determination and hard work, she created her own telescope and began her journey to explore the universe, one star at a time.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;在一个小镇上，有一个名叫米娅的小女孩，她对星星有一个疑问。她常常仰望夜空，想知道宇宙的实证真理。一天晚上，她的老师告诉她，星星象征着梦想和愿望。米娅受到启发，想要体现这些理想。她决定制造一个望远镜，更近距离地观察星星，认为知识优于无知。凭借决心和努力，她制作了自己的望远镜，并开始了探索宇宙的旅程，一颗星星一个星星地去观察。</description>
      <enclosure url="https://files.dwong.top/story/870e2ce6f8a90df81a73866f893f6a57.mp3" length="695040" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://files.dwong.top/story/870e2ce6f8a90df81a73866f893f6a57.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 16:02:28 +0800</pubDate>
      <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>2024-11-12</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>inquiry empirical symbolic embody dominant</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:image href="https://files.dwong.top/image/870e2ce6f8a90df81a73866f893f6a57.png"/>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
      <itunes:episode>88</itunes:episode>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024-11-11</title>
      <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top/2024-11-11.html</link>
      <description>organ occupation memorial daze deduce&amp;#10;&amp;#10;In a quiet town, there was a memorial dedicated to the brave soldiers who lost their lives during the war. Every year, on the anniversary of the day, the townspeople gathered to remember their sacrifices. This year, however, something unusual happened. As they placed flowers at the memorial, a mysterious organ music filled the air. The melody seemed to come from nowhere, causing everyone to stop and listen. People began to deduce that perhaps the spirits of the soldiers were with them, reminding them of their courage. The day turned into a celebration of life, rather than a day of sadness. They left with a renewed sense of appreciation for their freedom and the heroes who fought for it.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;在一个宁静的小镇上，有一个纪念碑，专门献给在战争中牺牲的勇敢士兵。每年，在这一天的周年纪念日，镇上的人们都会聚集在一起，缅怀他们的牺牲。然而，今年发生了一些不同寻常的事情。当他们在纪念碑上放置鲜花时，神秘的风琴音乐在空气中弥漫。旋律似乎来自无处，导致每个人停下来倾听。人们开始推测，也许士兵们的灵魂与他们同在，提醒他们勇气。这一天变成了生命的庆祝，而不是悲伤的日子。他们带着对自由和为之奋斗的英雄们的新认识离开。</description>
      <enclosure url="https://files.dwong.top/story/b5e443de4aa29dd97e2ea4fd334a7251.mp3" length="861120" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://files.dwong.top/story/b5e443de4aa29dd97e2ea4fd334a7251.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 16:02:10 +0800</pubDate>
      <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>2024-11-11</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>organ occupation memorial daze deduce</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:image href="https://files.dwong.top/image/b5e443de4aa29dd97e2ea4fd334a7251.png"/>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
      <itunes:episode>87</itunes:episode>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024-11-10</title>
      <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top/2024-11-10.html</link>
      <description>tactful versatile spice reassurance enquiry&amp;#10;&amp;#10;In a small town, a young chef named Mia was known for her tactful approach to cooking. She wanted to create a versatile menu that would satisfy everyone. One day, she received an enquiry from a local restaurant about her special spice blend. Mia felt a mixture of excitement and nervousness. To provide reassurance, she invited the restaurant owner to her kitchen to show how she used the spice. They spent hours experimenting with flavors, and by the end of the day, they created a dish that was full of life and taste. The restaurant owner was impressed and decided to feature Mia's creations on their menu, bringing joy to many.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;在一个小镇上，一位名叫米娅的年轻厨师以其得体的烹饪方式而闻名。她想要创造一个多功能的菜单，满足每个人的需求。一天，她收到了当地一家餐厅关于她特制香料混合物的询问。米娅感到兴奋和紧张交织在一起。为了提供安心，她邀请餐厅老板来到她的厨房，展示她如何使用香料。他们花了几个小时实验各种风味，到了最后，他们创造出一道充满生机与味道的菜肴。餐厅老板印象深刻，决定将米娅的作品放在菜单上，给许多人带来了快乐。</description>
      <enclosure url="https://files.dwong.top/story/af6c43802564d9c747caffdef7539299.mp3" length="763680" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://files.dwong.top/story/af6c43802564d9c747caffdef7539299.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 16:02:11 +0800</pubDate>
      <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>2024-11-10</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>tactful versatile spice reassurance enquiry</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:image href="https://files.dwong.top/image/af6c43802564d9c747caffdef7539299.png"/>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
      <itunes:episode>86</itunes:episode>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024-11-09</title>
      <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top/2024-11-09.html</link>
      <description>warehouse fury petty proceedings insomnia&amp;#10;&amp;#10;In a small town, there was a mysterious warehouse. Every night, loud noises came from it, causing insomnia among the nearby residents. Rumors spread that a group of petty thieves used the warehouse for their operations. One night, a brave girl named Lucy decided to investigate. She sneaked inside and discovered the thieves arguing in a fury over their stolen goods. Lucy quietly took pictures and reported them to the police. The next day, the police raided the warehouse, and the thieves were arrested. The town was safe again, and Lucy was hailed as a hero for her courageous actions.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;在一个小镇上，有一座神秘的仓库。每晚，从那里传出响亮的噪音，导致周围居民失眠。流言四起，传言一小群小偷在仓库里进行他们的活动。一天晚上，一个勇敢的女孩名叫露西决定调查她偷偷溜了进去，发现小偷们正在因他们偷来的赃物而愤怒地争吵。露西悄悄拍下照片，报告给警察。第二天，警察突袭了仓库，小偷们被抓住。小镇再次安全，露西因她的勇敢行为被称为英雄。</description>
      <enclosure url="https://files.dwong.top/story/a11d6d7b6def992978497a4501c7db7d.mp3" length="710880" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://files.dwong.top/story/a11d6d7b6def992978497a4501c7db7d.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 16:02:23 +0800</pubDate>
      <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>2024-11-09</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>warehouse fury petty proceedings insomnia</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:image href="https://files.dwong.top/image/a11d6d7b6def992978497a4501c7db7d.png"/>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
      <itunes:episode>85</itunes:episode>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024-11-08</title>
      <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top/2024-11-08.html</link>
      <description>loosen hazardous suspect outlet prosecute&amp;#10;&amp;#10;In a small town, there was a hazardous outlet that always caused trouble. The local residents began to suspect that it was linked to a series of accidents. One day, a brave teenager named Jack decided to investigate. He loosened the wires of the outlet and discovered that it was faulty and unsafe. Convinced that it was time to act, Jack reported his findings to the authorities. They decided to prosecute the company responsible for the outlet, ensuring that it would be fixed and prevent any more accidents. Thanks to Jack's courage, the town became a safer place for everyone.&amp;#10;&amp;#10;在一个小镇上，有一个危险的插座，总是惹麻烦。当地居民开始怀疑它与一系列事故有关。一天，一个勇敢的少年杰克决定调查。他松开了插座的电线，发现它有故障且不安全。杰克相信是时候采取行动，于是他向当局报告了自己的发现。他们决定起诉负责该插座的公司，确保它被修复，以防止更多事故。多亏了杰克的勇气，这个小镇成为了一个更安全的地方。</description>
      <enclosure url="https://files.dwong.top/story/65e877ea1974325af6e0a2b8dcf61671.mp3" length="721440" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://files.dwong.top/story/65e877ea1974325af6e0a2b8dcf61671.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 16:02:16 +0800</pubDate>
      <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>2024-11-08</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>loosen hazardous suspect outlet prosecute</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:image href="https://files.dwong.top/image/65e877ea1974325af6e0a2b8dcf61671.png"/>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
      <itunes:episode>84</itunes:episode>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024-11-07</title>
      <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top/2024-11-07.html</link>
      <description>arch inspection reasoning overnight agenda</description>
      <enclosure url="https://files.dwong.top/story/a60900f368c218bd4e37ddce80dd9f49.mp3" length="704640" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://files.dwong.top/story/a60900f368c218bd4e37ddce80dd9f49.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 16:02:14 +0800</pubDate>
      <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>2024-11-07</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>arch inspection reasoning overnight agenda</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:image href="https://daily-english.dwong.top/images/daily-words.png"/>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
      <itunes:episode>83</itunes:episode>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024-11-06</title>
      <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top/2024-11-06.html</link>
      <description>Daily words: momentum triumph debate incorporate coastline</description>
      <enclosure url="https://daily-english.dwong.top/audios/story/2024-11-06-english.mp3" length="627840" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://daily-english.dwong.top/audios/story/2024-11-06-english.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 16:01:49 +0800</pubDate>
      <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>2024-11-06</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Daily words: momentum triumph debate incorporate coastline</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:image href="https://daily-english.dwong.top/images/daily-words.png"/>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
      <itunes:episode>82</itunes:episode>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024-11-05</title>
      <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top/2024-11-05.html</link>
      <description>Daily words: devise ribbon pragmatic explosive rock</description>
      <enclosure url="https://daily-english.dwong.top/audios/story/2024-11-05-english.mp3" length="693120" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://daily-english.dwong.top/audios/story/2024-11-05-english.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 16:01:50 +0800</pubDate>
      <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>2024-11-05</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Daily words: devise ribbon pragmatic explosive rock</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:image href="https://daily-english.dwong.top/images/daily-words.png"/>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
      <itunes:episode>81</itunes:episode>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024-11-04</title>
      <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top/2024-11-04.html</link>
      <description>Daily words: ritual misinterpretation bureaucracy guarantee hostility</description>
      <enclosure url="https://daily-english.dwong.top/audios/story/2024-11-04-english.mp3" length="586560" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://daily-english.dwong.top/audios/story/2024-11-04-english.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 16:01:57 +0800</pubDate>
      <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>2024-11-04</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Daily words: ritual misinterpretation bureaucracy guarantee hostility</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:image href="https://daily-english.dwong.top/images/daily-words.png"/>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
      <itunes:episode>80</itunes:episode>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024-11-03</title>
      <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top/2024-11-03.html</link>
      <description>Daily words: negligence icily structure integrity endeavour</description>
      <enclosure url="https://daily-english.dwong.top/audios/story/2024-11-03-english.mp3" length="612000" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://daily-english.dwong.top/audios/story/2024-11-03-english.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 16:01:52 +0800</pubDate>
      <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>2024-11-03</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Daily words: negligence icily structure integrity endeavour</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:image href="https://daily-english.dwong.top/images/daily-words.png"/>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
      <itunes:episode>79</itunes:episode>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024-11-02</title>
      <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top/2024-11-02.html</link>
      <description>Daily words: laid-back influx resilience blindness profoundly</description>
      <enclosure url="https://daily-english.dwong.top/audios/story/2024-11-02-english.mp3" length="685440" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://daily-english.dwong.top/audios/story/2024-11-02-english.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 16:01:55 +0800</pubDate>
      <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>2024-11-02</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Daily words: laid-back influx resilience blindness profoundly</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:image href="https://daily-english.dwong.top/images/daily-words.png"/>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
      <itunes:episode>78</itunes:episode>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024-11-01</title>
      <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top/2024-11-01.html</link>
      <description>Daily words: courteous orientation discourage consent interpretation</description>
      <enclosure url="https://daily-english.dwong.top/audios/story/2024-11-01-english.mp3" length="712320" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://daily-english.dwong.top/audios/story/2024-11-01-english.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 16:02:35 +0800</pubDate>
      <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>2024-11-01</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Daily words: courteous orientation discourage consent interpretation</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:image href="https://daily-english.dwong.top/images/daily-words.png"/>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
      <itunes:episode>77</itunes:episode>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024-10-31</title>
      <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top/2024-10-31.html</link>
      <description>Daily words: scarce imperative backward fragrance coherent</description>
      <enclosure url="https://daily-english.dwong.top/audios/story/2024-10-31-english.mp3" length="540480" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://daily-english.dwong.top/audios/story/2024-10-31-english.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 16:01:52 +0800</pubDate>
      <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>2024-10-31</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Daily words: scarce imperative backward fragrance coherent</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:image href="https://daily-english.dwong.top/images/daily-words.png"/>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
      <itunes:episode>76</itunes:episode>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024-10-30</title>
      <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top/2024-10-30.html</link>
      <description>Daily words: attachment reservation horrify hierarchical precedent</description>
      <enclosure url="https://daily-english.dwong.top/audios/story/2024-10-30-english.mp3" length="578400" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://daily-english.dwong.top/audios/story/2024-10-30-english.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 16:02:07 +0800</pubDate>
      <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>2024-10-30</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Daily words: attachment reservation horrify hierarchical precedent</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:image href="https://daily-english.dwong.top/images/daily-words.png"/>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
      <itunes:episode>75</itunes:episode>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024-10-29</title>
      <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top/2024-10-29.html</link>
      <description>Daily words: normality raid chapel avenue complication</description>
      <enclosure url="https://daily-english.dwong.top/audios/story/2024-10-29-english.mp3" length="521280" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://daily-english.dwong.top/audios/story/2024-10-29-english.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 16:01:48 +0800</pubDate>
      <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>2024-10-29</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Daily words: normality raid chapel avenue complication</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:image href="https://daily-english.dwong.top/images/daily-words.png"/>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
      <itunes:episode>74</itunes:episode>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024-10-28</title>
      <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top/2024-10-28.html</link>
      <description>Daily words: hang ironically vaccine desperate filter</description>
      <enclosure url="https://daily-english.dwong.top/audios/story/2024-10-28-english.mp3" length="665760" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://daily-english.dwong.top/audios/story/2024-10-28-english.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 16:02:45 +0800</pubDate>
      <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>2024-10-28</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Daily words: hang ironically vaccine desperate filter</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:image href="https://daily-english.dwong.top/images/daily-words.png"/>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
      <itunes:episode>73</itunes:episode>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024-10-27</title>
      <link>https://daily-english.dwong.top/2024-10-27.html</link>
      <description>Daily words: high-profile wave unrest ambiguous drain</description>
      <enclosure url="https://daily-english.dwong.top/audios/story/2024-10-27-english.mp3" length="647040" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid>https://daily-english.dwong.top/audios/story/2024-10-27-english.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 16:02:10 +0800</pubDate>
      <itunes:author>dwong</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>2024-10-27</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Daily words: high-profile wave unrest ambiguous drain</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:image href="https://daily-english.dwong.top/images/daily-words.png"/>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
      <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
      <itunes:episode>72</itunes:episode>
      <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>